<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE xml>
<T3locallang>
	<meta type="array">
		<description>Context Sensitive Help (CSH) for Flexform</description>
		<type>CSH</type>
		<csh_table>appointments_agenda</csh_table>
	</meta>
	<data type="array">
		<languageKey index="default" type="array">
			<label index="switchableControllerActions.description">Determines the view of the agenda. "Month" displays entire months, "Weeks" displays the configured amount of weeks.</label>
	   		<label index="settings.agendaUid.description">Pick the agenda to show, or set it to depend on the associated TypoScript constant.</label>
			<label index="settings.agendaNavOverride.description">It&apos;s possible to set how far back and forward you can navigate through the agenda. You can set the plugin to listen to flexform or to TypoScript values.</label>
			<label index="settings.agendaBack.description">By setting this, you allow the user to navigate a number of units back in the agenda, allowing to view anyone&apos;s appointments from previous times.</label>
			<label index="settings.agendaForward.description">By setting this, you allow the user to navigate a number of units forward in the agenda, allowing to view anyone&apos;s appointments ahead.</label>
			<label index="settings.agendaWeeksBeforeCurrent.description">Allows you to set how many weeks to display before the current week, when Agenda View is set to "Weeks".</label>
			<label index="settings.agendaWeeksAfterCurrent.description">Allows you to set how many weeks to display after the current week, when Agenda View is set to "Weeks".</label>
			<label index="settings.appointmentTypeList.description">Limit the appointment types shown on the agenda, or set it to depend on the associated TypoScript constant.</label>
			<label index="settings.allowCreate.description">Adds new appointment buttons to the agenda view, or set it to depend on the associated TypoScript constant.</label>
			<label index="settings.suGroup.description">Members of the Superuser Group have additional permissions and rights.</label>
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="nl" type="array">
			<label index="switchableControllerActions.description">Bepaalt de weergave van de agenda. "Maand" toont hele maanden, "Weken" toont het ingestelde aantal weken.</label>
	   		<label index="settings.agendaUid.description">Kies de agenda om te tonen, of laat het afhangen van de gerelateerde TypoScript constante.</label>
			<label index="settings.agendaNavOverride.description">Het is mogelijk in te stellen hoever vooruit en terug genavigeerd kan worden in de agenda. Deze instelling bepaalt of de plugin dit uitleest uit dit formulier of uit TypoScript.</label>
			<label index="settings.agendaBack.description">Deze instelling staat de gebruiker toe om het opgegeven aantal eenheden terug te navigeren in de agenda.</label>
			<label index="settings.agendaForward.description">Deze instelling staat de gebruiker toe om het opgegeven aantal eenheden vooruit te navigeren in de agenda.</label>
			<label index="settings.agendaWeeksBeforeCurrent.description">Deze instelling bepaalt hoeveel weken getoond worden vòòr de huidige week, indien de Agenda Weergave op "Weken" staat.</label>
			<label index="settings.agendaWeeksAfterCurrent.description">Deze instelling bepaalt hoeveel weken getoond worden ná de huidige week, indien de Agenda Weergave op "Weken" staat.</label>
			<label index="settings.appointmentTypeList.description">Beperk de toegestane afspraak typen die getoond worden op de agenda, of laat het afhangen van de gerelateerde TypoScript constante.</label>
			<label index="settings.allowCreate.description">Voegt nieuwe afspraak knoppen toe aan de Agenda Weergave, of laat het afhangen van de gerelateerde TypoScript constante.</label>
			<label index="settings.suGroup.description">Leden van de Superuser Groep hebben extra rechten.</label>
		</languageKey>
	</data>
</T3locallang>