<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<T3locallang>
	<meta type="array">
		<description>Context Sensitive Help (CSH) for table tx_appointments_domain_model_formfield</description>
		<type>CSH</type>
		<csh_table>tx_appointments_domain_model_formfield</csh_table>
	</meta>
	<data type="array">
		<languageKey index="default" type="array">
	   
			<label index="title.description">Internal field title</label>
			<label index="label.description">Field label as shown on Frontend</label>
			<label index="csh.description">Helptext shown on Frontend next to the field</label>
			<label index="validation_types.description">Validation types can force the field to be validated as the chosen types of content. If the field content does not match the validation type, the form will inform the user and not save until corrected.</label>
			<label index="field_type.description">The field type determines its appearance and input method</label>
			<label index="choices.description">Selection choices, one per line. You may define values that differ from their labels, if desired. See details for the different approaches.</label>
			<label index="choices.details">
				The choices represent value/label combinations for a select box. You may explicitly define values and labels, separated by a pipe character: |

				value1|label1
				value2|label2
				
				If the label and value are the same, you can explicitly define both like above, or omit either one:

				choice1|choice1
				choice2

				If you want to have a decorative or informative label that doesn&apos;t represent an actual value, you may provide an empty value:

				|Make a choice:
				yes
				no
				
				If the last example is combined with a &quot;Not Empty&quot; Validation Type, the user becomes required to choose either yes or no before he is able to save the appointment, because the first label shown has an empty value.
			</label>
			<label index="function.description">The function sets whether the field has a special meaning. If you choose to let it add time, it is highly recommended to add the &lt;strong&gt;Natural Number&lt;/strong&gt; Validation Type!</label>
			<label index="enable_field.description">The condition-field that enables the current field if the given value matches</label>
			<label index="enable_value.description">The condition-value is case-insensitive</label>
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="nl" type="array">
	   
			<label index="title.description">Interne veld titel</label>
			<label index="label.description">Veld label zoals getoond op Frontend</label>
			<label index="csh.description">Toelichting dat op de Frontend naast het veld wordt getoond</label>
			<label index="validation_types.description">Validatie types forceren een veld om zich te valideren als het gekozen type inhoud. Als een veld niet voldoet aan een validatie type, dan zal het formulier dit aangeven en niet opgeslagen worden voor dit gecorrigeerd is.</label>
			<label index="field_type.description">Het veld type bepaalt zijn uiterlijk en invoerwijze</label>
			<label index="choices.description">Selectie keuzes, per regel één. U kunt de waarden en labels van elkaar laten verschillen, indien gewenst. Zie details voor de verschillende methoden.</label>
			<label index="choices.details">
				De keuzes vertegenwoordigen waarde/label combinaties voor een selectie. U kunt expliciet een waarde en een label opgeven per keuze, gescheiden met een pipe: |

				waarde1|label1
				waarde2|label2
				
				Als de label en de waarde gelijk moeten zijn, kunt u zoals in het voorbeeld hierboven ze beiden expliciet noemen, of één van beiden weglaten:

				keuze1|keuze1
				keuze2

				Als u een decoratieve of informatieve label wilt die niet echt een daadwerkelijke waarde vertegenwoordigd, kunt u een lege waarde gebruiken:

				|Maak een keuze:
				ja
				nee
				
				Als het laatste voorbeeld gecombineerd is met een &quot;Vereist&quot; Validatie Type, dan is de gebruiker vereist om de ja of nee keuze te selecteren alvorens hij de afspraak kan opslaan, omdat de eerste label een lege waarde heeft.
			</label>
			<label index="function.description">De functie bepaalt of het veld een speciale betekenis heeft. Indien de keuze valt op het toevoegen van tijd, dan wordt sterk aanbevolen het &lt;strong&gt;Natuurlijk Getal&lt;/strong&gt; Validatie Type te kiezen!</label>
			<label index="enable_field.description">Het conditie-veld dat bij de opgegeven waarde het huidige veld activeert</label>
			<label index="enable_value.description">De conditie-waarde is hoofdletterongevoelig</label>
		</languageKey>
	</data>
</T3locallang>