<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<T3locallang>
	<meta type="array">
		<description>Context Sensitive Help (CSH) for table tx_appointments_domain_model_type</description>
		<type>CSH</type>
		<csh_table>tx_appointments_domain_model_type</csh_table>
	</meta>
	<data type="array">
		<languageKey index="default" type="array">
	   
			<label index="name.description">Name of appointment type</label>
			<label index="superuser_only.description">If enabled, only lets superusers create appointments of this type</label>
			<label index="exclusive_availability.description">If enabled, will make this type&apos;s availability be affected exclusively by appointments of its own type, on the same agenda</label>
			<label index="dont_block_types.description">If enabled, will make this type invisible to other types, on the same agenda</label>
			<label index="dont_restrict_type_counts.description">If enabled, will make this type not count to other types maximum allowed appointments (per X days), on the same agenda</label>
			<label index="default_duration.description">Number of minutes an appointment of this type takes, at minimum</label>
			<label index="start_time_monday.description">Earliest possible time to make appointments on Mondays, ranging from 00:00 to 23:59</label>
			<label index="start_time_tuesday.description">Earliest possible time to make appointments on Tuesdays, ranging from 00:00 to 23:59</label>
			<label index="start_time_wednesday.description">Earliest possible time to make appointments on Wednesdays, ranging from 00:00 to 23:59</label>
			<label index="start_time_thursday.description">Earliest possible time to make appointments on Thursdays, ranging from 00:00 to 23:59</label>
			<label index="start_time_friday.description">Earliest possible time to make appointments on Fridays, ranging from 00:00 to 23:59</label>
			<label index="start_time_saturday.description">Earliest possible time to make appointments on Saturdays, ranging from 00:00 to 23:59</label>
			<label index="start_time_sunday.description">Earliest possible time to make appointments on Sundays, ranging from 00:00 to 23:59</label>
			<label index="stop_time_monday.description">Latest possible time to make appointments on Mondays, ranging from 00:00 to 23:59</label>
			<label index="stop_time_tuesday.description">Latest possible time to make appointments on Tuesdays, ranging from 00:00 to 23:59</label>
			<label index="stop_time_wednesday.description">Latest possible time to make appointments on Wednesdays, ranging from 00:00 to 23:59</label>
			<label index="stop_time_thursday.description">Latest possible time to make appointments on Thursdays, ranging from 00:00 to 23:59</label>
			<label index="stop_time_friday.description">Latest possible time to make appointments on Fridays, ranging from 00:00 to 23:59</label>
			<label index="stop_time_saturday.description">Latest possible time to make appointments on Saturdays, ranging from 00:00 to 23:59</label>
			<label index="stop_time_sunday.description">Latest possible time to make appointments on Sundays, ranging from 00:00 to 23:59</label>
			<label index="exclude_holidays.description">If enabled, does not allow appointments on days marked as holiday in the agenda record</label>
			<label index="max_amount_monday.description">Number of appointments allowed on Mondays (empty = 0!)</label>
			<label index="max_amount_tuesday.description">Number of appointments allowed on Tuesdays (empty = 0!)</label>
			<label index="max_amount_wednesday.description">Number of appointments allowed on Wednesdays (empty = 0!)</label>
			<label index="max_amount_thursday.description">Number of appointments allowed on Thursdays (empty = 0!)</label>
			<label index="max_amount_friday.description">Number of appointments allowed on Fridays (empty = 0!)</label>
			<label index="max_amount_saturday.description">Number of appointments allowed on Saturdays (empty = 0!)</label>
			<label index="max_amount_sunday.description">Number of appointments allowed on Sundays (empty = 0!)</label>
			<label index="minute_interval_monday.description">Number of minutes between allowed appointment time-slots on Mondays</label>
			<label index="minute_interval_tuesday.description">Number of minutes between allowed appointment time-slots on Tuesdays</label>
			<label index="minute_interval_wednesday.description">Number of minutes between allowed appointment time-slots on Wednesdays</label>
			<label index="minute_interval_thursday.description">Number of minutes between allowed appointment time-slots on Thursdays</label>
			<label index="minute_interval_friday.description">Number of minutes between allowed appointment time-slots on Fridays</label>
			<label index="minute_interval_saturday.description">Number of minutes between allowed appointment time-slots on Saturdays</label>
			<label index="minute_interval_sunday.description">Number of minutes between allowed appointment time-slots on Sundays</label>
			<label index="max_amount_per_var_days.description">Overrules the allowed cumulative amount of appointments per X consecutive days, where the next field is X. &lt;strong&gt;CAUTION: Setting these inappropriately adversely affects available date/timeslots.&lt;/strong&gt;</label>
			<label index="per_var_days.description">.. per X consecutive days .. &lt;strong&gt;[see previous field]&lt;/strong&gt;</label>
			<label index="per_var_days_interval.description">If set, the number of hours before and after the cumulative amount of appointments to additionally block, if the appointments take place in consecutive timeblocks of this field&apos;s amount of hours. i.e. &apos;12&apos; would result in 12 hours before and after blocked if and only if the appointments take place in consecutive 12 hour blocks. &lt;strong&gt;CAUTION: Setting these inappropriately adversely affects performance.&lt;/strong&gt;</label>
			<label index="between_minutes.description">Number of minutes reserved before, after and/or between appointments</label>
			<label index="hours_mutable.description">Number of hours an appointment can be changed/deleted after being scheduled</label>
			<label index="blocked_hours.description">Number of hours until first available appointment time-slot</label>
			<label index="blocked_hours_workdays.description">Number of workday hours until first available appointment time-slot, in case blocked hours fall in weekend</label>
			<label index="max_days_forward.description">Maximum number of days forward available to schedule, counting from the first</label>
			<label index="form_fields.description">Form Fields for this appointment type</label>
		</languageKey>
		<languageKey index="nl" type="array">
	   
			<label index="name.description">Naam van afspraak type</label>
			<label index="superuser_only.description">Door dit te activeren, kunnen alleen superusers afspraken van dit type aanmaken</label>
			<label index="exclusive_availability.description">Door dit te activeren, zal de beschikbaarheid van dit type uitsluitend aangetast kunnen worden door afspraken van hetzelfde type, op dezelfde agenda</label>
			<label index="dont_block_types.description">Door dit te activeren, zal dit type onzichtbaar zijn voor andere typen, op dezelfde agenda</label>
			<label index="dont_restrict_type_counts.description">Door dit te activeren, zal dit type niet meetellen naar de maximale toegestane afspraken van andere typen (per X dagen), op dezelfde agenda</label>
			<label index="default_duration.description">Hoeveelheid minuten een afspraak van dit type minimaal in beslag neemt</label>
			<label index="start_time_monday.description">Vroegst mogelijke tijdstip om afspraken te plannen op Maandagen, van 00:00 tot 23:59</label>
			<label index="start_time_tuesday.description">Vroegst mogelijke tijdstip om afspraken te plannen op Dinsdagen, van 00:00 tot 23:59</label>
			<label index="start_time_wednesday.description">Vroegst mogelijke tijdstip om afspraken te plannen op Woensdagen, van 00:00 tot 23:59</label>
			<label index="start_time_thursday.description">Vroegst mogelijke tijdstip om afspraken te plannen op Donderdagen, van 00:00 tot 23:59</label>
			<label index="start_time_friday.description">Vroegst mogelijke tijdstip om afspraken te plannen op Vrijdagen, van 00:00 tot 23:59</label>
			<label index="start_time_saturday.description">Vroegst mogelijke tijdstip om afspraken te plannen op Zaterdagen, van 00:00 tot 23:59</label>
			<label index="start_time_sunday.description">Vroegst mogelijke tijdstip om afspraken te plannen op Zondagen, van 00:00 tot 23:59</label>
			<label index="stop_time_monday.description">Laatst mogelijke tijdstip om afspraken te plannen op Maandagen, van 00:00 tot 23:59</label>
			<label index="stop_time_tuesday.description">Laatst mogelijke tijdstip om afspraken te plannen op Dinsdagen, van 00:00 tot 23:59</label>
			<label index="stop_time_wednesday.description">Laatst mogelijke tijdstip om afspraken te plannen op Woensdagen, van 00:00 tot 23:59</label>
			<label index="stop_time_thursday.description">Laatst mogelijke tijdstip om afspraken te plannen op Donderdagen, van 00:00 tot 23:59</label>
			<label index="stop_time_friday.description">Laatst mogelijke tijdstip om afspraken te plannen op Vrijdagen, van 00:00 tot 23:59</label>
			<label index="stop_time_saturday.description">Laatst mogelijke tijdstip om afspraken te plannen op Zaterdagen, van 00:00 tot 23:59</label>
			<label index="stop_time_sunday.description">Laatst mogelijke tijdstip om afspraken te plannen op Zondagen, van 00:00 tot 23:59</label>
			<label index="exclude_holidays.description">Door dit te activeren, worden afspraken niet toegestaan op feestdagen ingesteld in de Agenda</label>
			<label index="max_amount_monday.description">Hoeveelheid afspraken toegestaan op Maandagen (leeg = 0!)</label>
			<label index="max_amount_tuesday.description">Hoeveelheid afspraken toegestaan op Dinsdagen (leeg = 0!)</label>
			<label index="max_amount_wednesday.description">Hoeveelheid afspraken toegestaan op Woensdagen (leeg = 0!)</label>
			<label index="max_amount_thursday.description">Hoeveelheid afspraken toegestaan op Donderdagen (leeg = 0!)</label>
			<label index="max_amount_friday.description">Hoeveelheid afspraken toegestaan op Vrijdagen (leeg = 0!)</label>
			<label index="max_amount_saturday.description">Hoeveelheid afspraken toegestaan op Zaterdagen (leeg = 0!)</label>
			<label index="max_amount_sunday.description">Hoeveelheid afspraken toegestaan op Zondagen (leeg = 0!)</label>
			<label index="minute_interval_monday.description">Hoeveelheid minuten tussen toegestane afspraak tijdssloten op Maandagen</label>
			<label index="minute_interval_tuesday.description">Hoeveelheid minuten tussen toegestane afspraak tijdssloten op Dinsdagen</label>
			<label index="minute_interval_wednesday.description">Hoeveelheid minuten tussen toegestane afspraak tijdssloten op Woensdagen</label>
			<label index="minute_interval_thursday.description">Hoeveelheid minuten tussen toegestane afspraak tijdssloten op Donderdagen</label>
			<label index="minute_interval_friday.description">Hoeveelheid minuten tussen toegestane afspraak tijdssloten op Vrijdagen</label>
			<label index="minute_interval_saturday.description">Hoeveelheid minuten tussen toegestane afspraak tijdssloten op Zaterdagen</label>
			<label index="minute_interval_sunday.description">Hoeveelheid minuten tussen toegestane afspraak tijdssloten op Zondagen</label>
			<label index="max_amount_per_var_days.description">Beheerste de toegestane hoeveelheid afspraken per X opeenvolgende dagen, waar X in het volgende veld wordt bepaald. &lt;strong&gt;LET OP: Het ontoepasselijk gebruik van deze velden kan de beschikbare datum/tijdsvakken negatief beïnvloeden.&lt;/strong&gt;</label>
			<label index="per_var_days.description">.. per X opeenvolgende dagen .. &lt;strong&gt;[zie vorig veld]&lt;/strong&gt;</label>
			<label index="per_var_days_interval.description">Indien ingevuld, het aantal uur vòòr en ná de totale hoeveelheid afspraken dat vrij moet blijven, mits de afspraken ook opeenvolgende tijdsblokken van dit aantal uur bezetten. vb. &apos;12&apos; zou 12 uur vòòr en ná vrijhouden, mits de afspraken plaatsvinden in opeenvolgende 12 uur tijdsblokken. &lt;strong&gt;LET OP: Het ontoepasselijk gebruik van deze velden kan de snelheidsprestaties schaden.&lt;/strong&gt;</label>
			<label index="between_minutes.description">Hoeveelheid minuten gereserveerd voor, na en/of tussen afspraken</label>
			<label index="hours_mutable.description">Hoeveelheid uren waarin toegestaan een afspraak nog te wijzigen/verwijderen, nadat deze is aangemaakt</label>
			<label index="blocked_hours.description">Hoeveelheid uren tot de eerste toegestane afspraak tijdsslot</label>
			<label index="blocked_hours_workdays.description">Hoeveelheid werkdag-uren tot de eerste toegestane afspraak tijdsslot, in geval de geblokkeerde uren in het weekend vallen</label>
			<label index="max_days_forward.description">Maximale hoeveelheid dagen vooruit waarin een afspraak gepland kan worden, tellend vanaf de eerst mogelijke</label>
			<label index="form_fields.description">Formulier Velden voor dit afspraken type</label>
		</languageKey>
	</data>
</T3locallang>